wpressblog.com 2019-04-01

# Privacy Policy | WPressBlog

You are here: [Home](https://www.wpressblog.com/) / Privacy Policy

 **Who we are**

Our website address is https://www.wpressblog.com.

At Wpressblog.com, we recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use visit Wpressblog.com, and how we safeguard your information. We never sell your personal information to third parties.

 **Log Files**

As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider, such as AOL or Shaw Cable), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site.

 **Cookies and Web Beacons**

We do use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit our site. This could include only showing you a popup once in your visit, or the ability to login to some of our features, such as forums.

 **Affiliate Disclosure Policy**

There is some cost involved in running this blog which includes hosting, design, paid tools and content services etc. To cover all these costs, from time to time, I used to place some affiliate links in my blog contents. It means I will earn a small commission when you buy a product using my affiliate link without any additional cost to you.

We also use third party advertisements on Wpressblog.com to support our site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google Adsense program) information including your IP address, your ISP, the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. This is generally used for geotargeting purposes or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited.

You can choose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts.

If you have any question or suggestion, please feel free to contact us using our email address: wpbloggers90 (at) gmail.com

## Reader Interactions
